Guide to the Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection 1903-1990s, bulk 1950s-1990s
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- 1998 donation
  - (Box 35)
    - Souvenirs (Los Angeles), 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 843-845)
    - KTVX: Beatles, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 846-847)
    - CNBC For Real story: Airplane auction, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 848)
    - KTVX, CNBC: Poinsettia 2, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 849)
    - KTVX: Million 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 850-851)
    - KTVX Sundance 1-4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 852-855)
    - KTVX: Hubcap 1-3, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 856-858)
    - Edna, mail carrier 1-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 859-861)
    - Toy soldier, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 862-863)
    - Sun Studios; Memphis, Tennessee 1-2, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 864-865)
    - Guldstrand Wirth, Sims 1-3, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 866-868)
    - Steals 'n deals, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 869)
    - CNBC: Hollywood cars 2, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 870)
    - CNBC: Beverly Hills hotel 2 (opening), 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 871)
    - Long Beach Grand Prix 3, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 872)
    - CNBC: Smog art, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 873)
    - CNBC Graphics - American, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 874)
    - Bones walk around; Katie Malone interview; Gift items; Cordell, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 875)
    - KTVX: Majestic 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 876)
    - National Forest, El Yuneue standup promo tape 1, Bill B. outtake, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 877)
    - CNBC: Napa Valley sunsets dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 878)
    - Ryba's fudge, final cut 178, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 879)
    - KTVX: Thanksgiving meal, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 880)
    - CNBC: Spinner triplets; Wrestling Linir Flyaway, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 881)
    - CNBC: Bloopers - Jeri Carturgh, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 882)
    - KTVX: Tent circus, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 883)
    - CNBC For Real story: Christa's umbrellas, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 884)
    - CNBC For Real story: School pictures Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 885)
  - (Box 36)
    - KTVX: Substitute for horror, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 886)
    - CNBC: John F. Kennedy 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 6, 7, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 887-893)
    - CNBC: Track, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 894-903)
    - KTVX: Audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 904-905)
    - CNBC: Revere, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 906-908)
    - CNBC Famous Footsteps: Washington crossing, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 909)
    - CNBC: Freedom March music dub from compact disc, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 910-911)
    - KTVX: Washington; Man H track 3, 4, 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 912)
    - Sushi tape 1, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 913)
    - Ski show new audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 914)
    - Travel Channel: Boston and Massachusets, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 915-916)
    - CNBC: Irving pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 917-918)
    - CNBC: Voiceover credit, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 919)
    - Numerous Versions of Washington, New York City, Tarrytown, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 920)
  - (Box 37)
    - KTVX: Donuts, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 921)
    - KTVX: 100 year-old, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 922-925)
    - KTVX: Governor's Mansion, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 926-928)
    - KTVX: Sand 2, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 929-930)
    - CNBC: Computer car painting 1-2, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 931-932)
    - CNBC: Power cars Chevrolet, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 933-935)
      More dora and B-roll
    - CNBC: Car design, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 936-937)
    - KTVX: Big Rock, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 938-939)
    - KTVX: High surplus, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 940-941)
    - KTVX: Driggs special, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 942-943)
    - KTVX: Taxes, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 944-945)
    - KTVX: Powow 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 946-947)
    - KTVX: Parowan, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 948)
    - KTVX: Dump, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 949)
    - KTVX: Frank Quest tape 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 950)
    - KTVX: Cruise night Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 951)
    - General Motors plant, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 952)
    - KTVX: Store, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 953)
    - CNBC: Car show tape 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 954)
    - KTVX: CBW, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 955)
    - KTVX: Victrolia, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 956)
    - KTVX: Trapper, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 957)
    - KTVX: Mooney 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 958)
    - Marie 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 959)
    - Power cars: Cadillac, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 960)
  - (Box 38)
    - KTVX: Russia, Berlin, Moscow missiles, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 961-984)
    - CNBC For Real story: Triplets, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 985)
    - CNBC For Real story: Cruise night, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 986)
    - CNBC: Gremlins football, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 987)
    - CNBC For Real story: B-25 bombers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 988)
    - KTVX: Giraffes, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 989)
    - CNBC: Condor release, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 990)
    - CNBC For Real story: Craig Wirth Los Angeles, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 991)
    - CNBC for news channel Craig Wirth, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 992)
    - CNBC For Real story: Ball split, Kids golf, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 993)
    - CNBC: Eclipse 1-2, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 994-996)
    - Iwerks, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 997)
    - CNBC For Real story: Juggling, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 998)
    - CNBC For Real story: Fall beauty, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 999)
    - CNBC For Real story: Sandcastles, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1000-1001)
  - (Box 39)
    - Splash B-roll behind the scenes 1-2, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1002-1003)
    - Passion fruit 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1004-1005)
    - Tootsie Roll 1-3, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1006-1007)
    - Old mill 1-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1008-1011)
    - Motor cowboy 1, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1012-1014)
    - Mining 3-4, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1015-1016)
    - WCCL TV New Orleans, Louisiana, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1017-1020)
    - Mask 1and 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1021-1022)
    - Ryba's fudge, Grand Hotel 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1023-1024)
    - Pabst standup 1-2, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1025-1026)
    - Polka Milwaukee, Wisconsin land 2, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1027-1029)
    - Del Morro tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1030)
    - John Espy; Ranchee, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1031-1034)
    - ESS'S for Southwest Air, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1035-1036)
    - Sun Studios, Memphis Tennesse 3, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1037)
    - CNBC For Real story: Theme shop, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1038)
    - Drive through bank; McDonald's; Dairy; drive-in restaurant, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1039)
    - CNBC: Celebrity art auction; New channel, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1040)
    - CNBC: Synchronized swimming, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1041)
    - CNBC: Giraffes, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1042)
    - CNBC: Iwerks, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1043)
  - (Box 40)
    - CNBC: Toys, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1044-1046)
    - Toy executive, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1047)
    - CNBC: Spinning, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1048)
    - CNBC: Long Beach 1-2, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1049)
    - Pete Ellis tape 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1050)
    - CNBC: The edge, 1997; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1051)
    - Imperial palace 1, 3, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1052)
    - Compu car art 3, 4, 5, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1053-1055)
    - Baseball: New York Mets' P. Rico 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1056)
    - CNBC: Navigate 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1057)
    - University of Southern California cinema school 6, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1058)
    - Long Beach Grand Prix 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1059)
    - CNBC: Emit; Disney, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1060)
    - People finders B-roll 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1061)
    - CNBC: Sales tape dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1062)
    - KTVX: Otto, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1063)
    - CNBC: Invention convention, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1064)
    - CNBC: Conventions, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1065)
    - Kanab movie 1, 2, 4, 5, 8, 9, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1066-1072)
    - KTVX: Cop history 2, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1073)
    - KTVX: Santaquin 1, 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1074-1075)
    - KTVX: Gilligan 1, 2, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1076-1078)
    - KTVX: Weekly newspaper 1, 2, 3, 4, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1079-1081)
    - Edna: Mail carrier, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1082)
    - KTVX: Hilltop, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1083)
    - KTVX: Farm, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1084)
    - KTVX: Sand 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1085)
  - (Box 41)
    - CNBC: Superbowl merchandise, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1086)
    - Float 1-2, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1087)
    - KTVX: San Diego cars, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1088)
    - CNBC: Hollywood cars, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1089)
    - Walk of Rock standup, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1090)
    - Baseball, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1091)
    - Cadillac television footage, channel 1, 1995; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1092)
    - Cadillac press release, product reel, 1994; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1093)
    - Antique automobile run, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1094)
  - (Box 42)
    - Chapel; Las Vegas, Nevada 1-3, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1095-1097)
    - Laughlin, Nevada, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1098-1100)
    - Cotton's Northwoods, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1101-1102)
    - Dell Computers, Austin, Texas, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1103-1105)
    - Lionel Trains, Mt. Clemens, Michigan, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1106-1108)
    - Mary Kay, Dallas, Texas, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1109-1112)
    - Domino's Pizza, Tom Monohan; Detroit Tigers; Ann Arbor, Michigan, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1113-1118)
    - Helicopter, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1119)
    - Mining, Helena, Montana 1-2, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1120-1121)
  - (Box 43)
    - Elvis Tupelo, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1122-1143)
    - CNBC: Graceland, handout, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1144-1148)
  - (Box 44)
    - Holland Lake Lodge, Montana 2, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1149)
    - Bus drive-by, bus leaving Wang building, Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1150)
    - D.I.C., 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1151-1154)
    - On the Map: Memphis; Detroit, Michigan, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1155-1156)
    - On the Map: Great Falls, Montana, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1157)
    - REI, Seattle, Washington 3, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1159)
    - CNBC: Tape 100, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1160)
    - Boston B-roll, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1161)
    - Video Wisconsin: Tommy Bartlett Show, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1162)
    - CNBC: Revere house, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1163-1169)
    - CNBC: Pony, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1170-1178)
  - (Box 45)
    - CNBC: Famous Footsteps; Variety, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1179-1189)
    - KTVX: Graphics and maps, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1190)
    - Graphics, revised map, animated and old map, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1191)
    - KTVX: TTC promos, 1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1192)
    - CNBC: Sweeten, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1193)
    - CNBC: Home cooking; slate, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1194)
    - KTVX: Credits, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1195-1198)
    - CNBC, KTVS: Pony Express, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1199-1204)
    - KTVX: Lewis and Clark raw footage, 1993; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1205-1222)
    - CNBC: LAX airport slate, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1223)
  - (Box 46)
    - KTVX: Dive, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1224-1225)
    - KTVX: Sugar House complete story, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1226-1229)
    - KTVX: Race car, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1230-1231)
    - CNBC: Last cigarette advertisement, 1972; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1232)
    - KTVX: Mushroom, Park City, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1233-1238)
    - Torrey, Utah old meeting house, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1239-1240)
    - Last American Camaro, General Motors closes Van Nuys plant, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1241)
    - Beaver Court House audio, Hudson, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1242-1243)
    - KTVX: Cramer, 1988; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1244-1245)
    - Juggling at Trolley Square, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1246)
    - KTVX: Synchronized swimming, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1247)
    - Internal Revenue Service (IRS) Ogden office, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1248)
    - Lambs Grill downtown Salt Lake City, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1249)
    - Salt Palace tear down cut, 1993-1994; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1250)
    - Video of progress in Utah (long), 1956; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1251-1252)
  - (Box 47)
    - CNBC: Barbie; Los Angeles, 1987; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1253)
    - KTVX: Old electrons, JD Williams, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1254)
    - KTVX: The Smothers Brothers, undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1255)
    - KTVX: Triplets; dating 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1256)
    - Kids doing Thanksgiving at Jordan, thank you, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1257)
    - FNN: Wyoming mail carrier Edna, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1258)
    - Hockey, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1259)
    - B-25 bombers 1 of 2, Los Angeles, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1260)
    - Musk for first graph, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1261)
    - KTVX: Ti kawan do 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1262-1263)
      Wirth learns to break boards
    - KTVX: Flagger 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1264)
    - KTVX: Sail plane 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1265)
    - KTVX: Elevator repairman, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1266)
    - KTVX: Spent the day in prison, 1990's; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1267)
    - KTVX: Pee wee football 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1268)
    - KTVX: Sugar House kids sled 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1269)
    - Floating on Great Salt Lake, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1270)
    - KTVX: Olster, Ireland to reform, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1271)
    - Daily World War II footage, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1272)
    - Wirth flying B-17 bomber, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1273)
    - Owner of raccoon, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1274)
    - Home new opens, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1275)
    - West Jordan kite club, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1276)
    - Rex the pig 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1277)
    - KTVX: Hot time, terrible jobs in the summer 1-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1278-1280)
  - (Box 48)
    - KTVX: T-ball, Sandy, 1997; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1281)
    - On The Map: Silver City, New Mexico; Pinos, Altos, Sante Rita, New Mexico, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1282)
      Old continental divide about copper pit
    - KTVX: Utah slang, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1283)
    - Employment, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1284)
    - KTVX: Tigers at Hogle Zoo 1, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1285)
    - KTVX: Building and tearing down Great America circus, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1286-1287)
    - KTVX: Salt Lake County farm 3 of 4, 1988; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1288)
    - KTVX: Train 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1289)
    - Interurban film: Flight of the century Chicago, to New York 1935, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1290)
    - KTVX: Spins everything on the finger, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1291)
    - KTVX: Mail carrier; dairy, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1292)
    - Gardner mill, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1293)
    - KTVX: Bowling, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1294)
    - KTVX: 6th grade Christmas, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1295-1296)
    - CNBC: Celebrity art auction, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1297)
    - KTVX: Egg prop, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1298-1299)
    - Olympics not awarded to Salt Lake City, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1300-1301)
    - World War II, 1988; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1302-1303)
    - KTVX: Ellis Armstrong, father of the interstate, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1304-1305)
    - KTVX: Chuck-A-Rama 2-3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1306-1307)
    - KTVX: Farm, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1308)
    - KTVX: Christo's UMBRELLA, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1309)
    - KTVX: Handicap learn skills (Work Act) 2-3, 1989; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1310-1311)
    - KTVX: Ben Lowman Hotel 2-3, 1992; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1312-1313)
    - KTVX: Tearing down the Salt Palace, 1995; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1314-1316)
  - (Box 49)
    - Carribean wind surfing 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1317)
    - Smoky Mountain, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1318)
    - Grosso-Jacobson, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1319)
      A family for Joe, the medium.
    - Channel 2 soap opera: Young and the Restless, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1320)
    - Salt water taffy 1 of 3, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1321)
    - FNN: Virgelle Ferry and the buzzer out, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1322)
    - Wilcox incident; Phil and John T. Nielson one on one, 1987; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1323)
    - Dr. Bruce Vorhauer interview B-roll 1, 2, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1324-1326)
      Salmon Lake, Montana
    - Gates of the Mountains tour B-roll, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1327-1329)
      Tour and guide
    - KTVX: Buffalo, Sagewood, Otto's babies raw footage, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1330)
    - Space needle, Seattle, Washington, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1331-1334)
  - (Box 50)
    - American minutes, travel expert, undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1335)
    - Tourism master, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1336)
    - KTVX: Milkman 1-2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1337-1338)
    - Sagewood, Otto's babies, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1339)
    - KTVX: Alf Engen at Alta, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1340)
    - KTVX: Consumer electronics show, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1341)
    - CNBC: High school farm, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1342)
    - Salt Palace stars W.C., undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1343)
    - FNN: Wind surf dug 1-2, 1991; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1344-1346)
    - Stream 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1347)
    - FNN: Virgelle Ferry, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1348)
    - Art development, Rampton Phillips gallery, 1971; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1349)
    - Copyright infrigement, 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 1350)
    - On the Map: Texarkana, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1351)
    - Aircx auto byte 1 (long), 1997; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1352)
    - Tower City, market 1-2, 1990; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1353)
- 2002 addendum
  - (Box 51)
    - Fire, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1354-1356)
    - Eagle, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1357)
    - Bluff Cemetery, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1358)
    - McCullough's arena pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1359)
    - Women's underwear, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1360)
    - Trolley, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1361)
    - Circus, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1362-1365)
    - Wendover, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1366-1369)
    - East 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1370)
    - Flight simulator, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1371-1372)
    - Drive-in, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1373)
    - Pool seniors, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1374-1375)
    - Drive-in, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1376-1382)
    - Pump, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1383-1384)
    - Ace, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1385)
    - Ben Loward, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1386)
    - Kid swim, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1387)
    - Bird show, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1388)
    - Lehi Roller Mills, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1389-1391)
    - Moll track 201, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1392)
    - Air patrol, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1393)
    - Photo fall, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1394-1396)
    - Alta football, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1397-1399)
    - Thanksgiving, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1400-1402)
    - Drive-in, Wirth audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1403)
    - Hold D-V, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1404)
    - Glad, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1405-1406)
    - Downtown, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1407-1409)
    - KTVX: 50 years air checks 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1410)
    - Gladiator, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1411)
    - Rokich-extra, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1412)
    - Cough drop, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1413)
    - Weeds, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1414)
    - Dog, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1415-1416)